# Mitchell Levy mitchlevy@gmail.com - (650) 302-0152

My goal is to move into the progressive, exciting industry of animation, with opportunities for upward mobility. In my past work experience, I've proven that my skillset includes teachability, adaptability, and being a reliable teammate. These skills, when combined with my attention to detail and my patient, empathetic approach to communication, make me the perfect candidate for production.

## Education + Certifications

## UCLA School of Medicine, Prehospital Medical Center

Graduate 2014

# University of Oregon

Journalism; No Degree 2002-2004

# Mountain View High School

Graduate 1999-2002

#### CrossFit

Level 1 Trainer

#### **Precision Nutrition**

Level 1 Nutritionist

#### American Heart Association

CPR for the Professional Rescuer

## Professional Assoc. of Diving Instructors

Open Water SCUBA Diver

#### National Registry of Emergecy Medical Technicians: EMT

Los Angeles County (inactive)

#### **American Red Cross**

CPR/First Aid Instructor (inactive)

# Familiarity + Skills

Microsoft Suite Google Suite; gMail Adobe CC; Photoshop, Premiere Pro After Effects, Illustrator, Acrobat Storyboard Pro, Shotgun HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python Scheduling, Calendar Keeping Note taking, Listening Public Speaking, Problem Solving

# Other Experiences

#### Swimming, Strength & Conditioning Coach

Valley Academy of Art & Science (Sept 2012 - Jan 2015)

## Wilderness Survival & Self Reliance School

St. George, Utah (Jan 2007 - April 2007)

# Work Experience

July 2017 - Present

## Gym Manager, Program Director, Personal Trainer

CrossFit High Voltage [Formerly Modern Viking Athletics] - Burbank, CA

Managed day-to-day operations of the 200+ member gym by organizing schedules, programs, staffing, equipment purchases, and events. Designed and deployed a highly successful on-site and online coaching program with a fully custom web app. Used organizational and progress tracking software to track improvements and trajectories of all clients. Fostered growth in clients through well-crafted programming, and patient, honest support. Helped to instruct new and experienced staff in gym operations.

January 2015 - August 2017

Emergency Medical Technician McCormick Ambulance - Torrance, CA

June 2014 - January 2015

# Emergency Medical Technician MedResponse Ambulance - Van Nuys, CA

Responded quickly and safely to 911 emergencies. Worked effectively in a team environment to provide life-saving care calmly and professionally under extreme stress. Utilized a warm and friendly demeanor to empathize with patients. Adapted to challenges and grew from supervisor feedback. Awarded LA County honors for excellence in lifesaving.

March 2009 - September 2009, September 2012 - June 2014

**Lifeguard Supervisor, Swim Instructor** Aquatic Safety Instruction - Northridge, CA Managed acquisitions, scheduling, and training of lifeguard team. Taught instructional swim for children and adults of all developmental and skill levels. Created training seminars for non-lifeguard summer camp and school staff to cultivate a safer pool

environment and to better manage emergency situations.

September 2009 - September 2012

House Manager, Recovery Coach Sober College - Woodland Hills, CA

Provided general oversight to ensure safety and well-being of clients. Managed staff roles and schedules in the recovery house. Organized school and clinical schedules for clients. Taught life skills, cooking, cleaning, budgeting, schedule keeping to house members. Tracked client progress with daily notes and maintained progress and case notes database.

June 2004 - February 2009

Teacher, Counselor, Director Eugene Family YMCA - Eugene, ORt

Designed and organized summer camp and after school youth programs for at-risk kids. Led 40-student outdoor adventures and backpacking trips. Lead elementary aged afterschool classroom. Communicated and planned with teachers, students, and parents to create best environment for success.